it turns out If 14 million - it’s the mother who
получается Если 14 млн - это се мама
takes it, it’s the mother who decides what
забирает уже мама она Сама решает на что
she will spend it on. Yes, 2 million is spent on an apartment
она потратит Да 2 млн уходит на квартиру
and five is left for p. Well, I don’t know, 5 million
и пять остаётся за п Ну я не знаю 5 млн
is 50,000 dollars or
это 50.000 долларов или Тоту Camry
you’ll buy a Totu Camry Well, in general, I would like a
купишь Ну вообще я хотела бы себе
BMW
BMW
Hello  zra I’m originally from Rostov,
Здравствуйте зра Я сам родом из Ростова
but I’ve been living in California for 18 years, 2 years later I’m
но уже 18 лет живу в Калифорнии через 2
from in the Rostov region
откуда Ростовской области
from where I’m from in the Rostov region, Rostov is coming
откуда С Ростовской области Ростов нану
straight from
прямо из
Rostov from Rostov, it’s cool My
Ростова из Ростова прикольно У меня
parents are still there What do
родители там ещё остались О чём
you communicate about
общаетесь
and with everyone differently who
да со всеми по-разному на кого
you study for  I’ve already graduated, I studied at
учитесь Я уже отучилась я училась на по
confectioner’s slama,
кондитера сламе
of course, what is your favorite
конечно а что какая самая ваша любимая
sweet that you can
сладость которую можете
make Ringo roll what kind of
сделать Ринго вый рулет какой
roll is Ringo Ringo what is it
рулет Ринго Ринго вый а что это такое
And without at least once tried
А без хоть раз пробовали
what
что
without without
без без
Yes, this is a nut from
Да это орехо из
what the basis for is made  meringue is the
то что вот делается основа для безе это
same base
та же основа
for meringue meringue go I don’t
для меренги меренги го правильно уже не
remember correctly and it’s laid out in a layer on a
помню и она выкладывается пластом на
baking sheet I don’t remember just how long it’s
противень я не помню только сколько она
baked and then you add your
выпекается и потом там добавляешь свою
filling and wrap it all up
начинку и всё это заворачиваю вот она
here it’s a cool roll What are you talking about
прикольно О чём тут общаетесь
differently
со по-разному
with
со
me?  Well, you see, we discussed
мной ну вот видите мы с вами обсудили
Ringo roll Well, come on, I think we did
Ринго рулет Ну давайте я думаю мы сюда
n’t come here for the ring roll, I
не за рингом рулетом пришли я так
think so. I just got bored in America. We
думаю Мне просто скучно стало в Америке
were once there,
были
not even once, but I
когда-то нет ни разу а тели
would really like to
бы очень хочу
see them in Russia. I like both  It’s
по мне и в России нравится И то И здесь
also beautiful here, how much is your
тоже красиво сколько у вас
salary? And I
зарплата А я не
don’t work, what do you live for? And my husband
работаю за что живёте А меня муж
provides for
обеспечивает
me;  I
м меня муж обеспечивает
somehow don’t raise this topic with
Украину я эту тему как-то не поднимаю с
anyone because I raised it,
кем потому что я её поднял
I don’t discuss it.
я её не обсуждаю
Okay, I like to instill such depraved
Ладно я люблю насаждать такие развратные
topics on young girls,
темы девушкам
I can’t say anything about this,
я ничего не могу сказать по этому
can you help me? Come on, I believe, tell me,
поможешь ты сможешь давай я верю скажи а
what should I say about this? Well, tell me
что я по этому поводу скаж Ну скаж
for example, either you will support this or,
например или тебе ты поддержишь это или
on the contrary, you don’t support it, I can just
наоборот не поддерживаешь это ж просто
say
сказать
this, I can say this,
могу такое сказать
why can’t I say it? Well, tell me, dear
почему не могу сказать Ну скажи милашка
Tell me why,
Скажи а почему
why don’t I want to? That is, you came here
почему не хочу То есть ты пришла тут
to talk. In short, they ask you about
поразговаривать Да короче а тебе про
the war. Why are
войну спрашивают
n’t you starving, your
не голодаешь
husband is on duty?  And what does this have to do with it? Well,
муж на вахте А это тут причём Ну это
in any case, the husband is on shift, how long has the husband been on shift
по-любому муж на вахте сколько муж на
for about two weeks, about two weeks, you already have
уже недели две о недели две у тебя уже
an itch like, yes, and you’ll already go out
короче зачесался типа да и ты уже выйду
now, in short, to chat roulette if it’s not
сейчас короче в чат рулетку если не
normal, girls talk about politics
нормально девчонки о политике общаются
when the husband is on shift A  this is damn
когда муж на вахте А это блин
so
такая
sweaty Damn let's okay okay my husband is in the
пото Блин давайте ладно окей мой муж
military so I don't discuss politics
военный поэтому я не обсуждаю политику
here I am because I can see it in your eyes when
вот я потому что я вижу по глазам когда
I asked who you work for you picked it up and
я спросил кем работаешь ты подняла и
started thinking about what to say and then
начала думать что сказать и потом
said shift worker well I can see that
сказала вахтовик ну я ж вижу я в том что
I'm a psychologist  I’m a doctor of psychology, so I
я психолог Я доктор психологии вот я в
teach at the University of California, that is, well,
университете Калифорнии преподаю то есть
I have such things Damn, when a person
ну у меня такие вещи Блин когда человек
can be seen when he is
видно когда он
deceiving, so I don’t discuss this
обманывает поэтому я не обсуждаю эту
topic and my husband is now on his own. And where in the unit? Well,
тему а муж сейчас на сво
like, how come he wasn’t taken to
типа как как его не забрали на
his place, he’s like  Well, he’s like a tank pilot Who is
сво он типа Ну он как лётчик танкист Кто
he, the
он
Aerospace Forces Aerospace Forces, it’s
ВКС воздушно-космические силы это
like, what are they doing, I don’t quite know what they’re
типа что они делают не совсем знаю что в
doing in Russia I haven’t lived in Russia for 18 years,
России делаю Я уже 18 лет не живу в
I don’t know either Well, it
России я тоже не знаю Ну это они
turns out that they’re shooting you down with some kind of satellites
получается что тебя спутники какие-то
or satellites  ko look
там сбивают или спутниками ко смотрят
that Yes, they’re not even for satellites or
что Да они даже за спутники ничего или
it’s air defense like what they are he doesn’t
это ПВО типа что они ти он мне не
tell me it’s all that’s why I don’t know I
рассказывает это всё я поэтому не знаю
understand How is he even worried that
понял А как он вообще переживает что
they can send him to his
могут отправить на сво
no and If they send you,
нет а Если отправят ты переживаешь
of course you’re worried because it’s my husband Unknown
конечно пото что это мой муж Неизвестно
what will happen to him there Do you
что с ним там произойдёт А у тебя есть
already have some friends who
уже какие-то знакомые которые
died, fortunately there is no such thing, wounded and
погибли к счастью такого нету раненые и
no,
не
I’m just wondering how you
нету мне интересно просто вот как ты
feel about the fact that there is a War and
относишься Да к тому что идёт Война и
your husband could be taken away and thrown to
твоего мужа могут забрать и кинуть
die in
умереть в
Ukraine I Well  Yes, of course I’m worried about my
Украине я Ну да я конечно переживаю за
husband because there’s no telling what
мужа потому что там Неизвестно что с
will happen to you in 5-10 minutes.
тобой через 5-10 минут произойдёт
Well, that’s it. Well, yes, have there already been drone flights to your city
Ну всё Ну да а к вам в город уже были
or
прилёты беспилотников или
not? Well, I don’t know about that,
нет Ну я за это не знаю
honestly I’m keeping an eye on it. Ida And from Rostov, yes, in
честно слежу Ида А из Ростова же да в
Rostov  if the Rostov region were not in
Ростове бы Ростовская область была не в
Rostov itself, it seems, it didn’t fly to our
Ростов сам вроде не прилетала у нас в
Shakhty, it
Шахты прилетала
flew closer to Volgograd, that Volgodonsk, in my opinion, it flew somewhere Yes, Volgodonsk is
по-моему где-то прилетала Да Волгодонск
closer to Volgograd, I don’t mean, and it
ближе к Волгограду не не имею в виду и к
flew closer to Volgograd Yes, and it flew to
Волгограду ближе прилетала Да и в
Volgodonsk
Волгодонск
So this oil depot was
прилетала Так что и нефтебаза вот эта
burning, in short,
горела короче
and the prodrug was really harsh. Well,
да пролекарство это прям жёстко было Ну
my mother skidded photos
у меня у меня мамка скида фотки
that said that in Rostov there was even
что говорила что в Ростове смок даже
a smell of smoke,
стоял запах
I don’t know, well, I’m
был я не знаю вот Ну я сейчас на данный
not in Rostov at the moment And so I’m with
момент не в Ростове нахожусь А так я с
Rostov, I’m in Krasny
Ростова я нахожусь в Красном
Sulina Sulina, this didn’t happen, I don’t feel
Сулине Сулине такого не было я не чувст
for My mother, the thing is that my mother is
за У меня мама меня дело в том что мама
allergic, she very immediately feels such
аллергик она очень сразу чувствует такие
things, she is allergic to
вещи у неё аллергия на продукты
combustion products, they showed what you see from the
горения показывали то что видите с
proletarsk right up to the red, it all
пролетарска аж до красного это всё
came to me, I understood  for example, you
дошло понял а это вот например у тебя
have friends who also have
знакомые есть тоже у которых мужья
military husbands. Well, I can tell you that a former young
военные Ну у меня сказать бывший молодой
man was mobilized and who
человек мобилизованный а он кто по
was his profession? Masha worked Well, yes, and before that he
был ль Маше работал Ну да а до этого он
served, too, the contract ended, the
Служил тоже контракт закончился
work came, mobilization was taken away, well,
работа пришла мобилизация забрали
yes, I already have Odnoklassnian  died
как Ну да у меня Одноклассник уже погиб
Yes,
есть
well, like, I feel like I’m 18 years old Well, I
Да ну типа как се чувствую я 18 лет Ну
didn’t even communicate, well, after school I
не общался даже ну как после школы даже
didn’t even communicate, you just know Classmates
не общался просто знаешь Одноклассники
there in the chat we have in the telegram, they
там в чат у нас есть в телеграме
wrote that then he died, in short, he
написали да что тогда погиб короче его
also had mobile phones Zro was sent to the Zaporozhye
тоже мобили Зро отправили в запорожскую
region and he got a Drone  flew in short Straight
область и ему Дрон прилетел короче Прямо
to the forehead Straight to the forehead in short this video was even
в лоб Прямо в лоб короче это видео даже
dropped on these Ukrainian resources
скидывали на этих украинских ресурсах
there are already laughing Yes in short he is running running
там аж смеются Да короче он бежит бежит
from this drone yes and the Drone is just
от этого дрона да а Дрон Прямо его так
catching up with him he is already catching up with
догоняет догоняет он уже такой разра
some kind of stick he is trying to fight off the drone
какой-то палкой пробует отбиваться дрона
and straight  his head was blown off in the head It’s
сти и прямо ему в лобешник разлетелась
terrible that my
башка Жуть у меня у
classmate in
одноклассника на
Ukraine was looking for him for a very long time because
Украине ну его очень долго искали потому
he died in December But
декабре погиб он А вот
only this year it
только в этом году
froze Oh yes, it just broke, the
о зависла О да просто оборвалась это
connection froze, they didn’t finish
связь зависла не
speaking, so at the beginning of the year it was normal, what’s wrong
договорили так нача нормально года то
with this
что с этим
guy  Well, it was only in the month of May that they
парнем Ну отца только аж в мае месяце
found him there until the last time, like they
нашли там до последнего типа такие типа
hoped that he was alive, but they weren’t. And
надеялись то что он живой А такие нет А
in what form he was already decomposed
в какой форме его на там уже разложился
there, honestly, I don’t know. In what form he
честно я не знаю В какой форме его там
was found there, so I wasn’t even present at the funeral.
нашли вот я даже на похоронах не
This  Most likely, they
присутствовала Это скорее всего Там
just found bones, a skull, they found
просто нашли кости череп нашли и
a badge, well, there was so much cold there.
жетон Ну там же сколько холода были
Maybe something was preserved there, maybe what? And
Может что-то там сохранилось может и что
how did his mom, like, well, how did his dad’s wife
А как его типа ну мама типа ну как жена
take it?
этого бати восприняла
Well, my mom was at the funeral. Like, she
Ну Моя мама была на похоронах Типа она
says, well, I naturally  she arrived soon, she
говорит Ну я естественно приезжала скоро
injected a sedative, she was sitting there, it
уколола успокоитель она там сидела
was just like that, and it’s true that I’m
просто так было а это правда что типа
paying 14 million for the
выплачиваю 14 Милн за
dead, what’s the truth, that for the
погибшего что что правда что за
dead they pay relatives 14
погибшего выплачивают родственникам 14
million
млн
rubles 14 yes,
руб 14 да
I know only for five five I heard
Я знаю только за пять пять я слышал
I just talked to a girl, she
Просто я общался с девочкой у неё
turns out to be a boyfriend  not the guy but the father died,
получается парень не парень а отец погиб
then they paid 14 million to his mother because
то выплатили 14 млн его маме потому что
he
он
and his wife were divorced and it turns out that this is her
с женой разведён и получается вот Это её
mother, his mother, then her grandmother
мама его мама то её бабушка себе
kept seven for herself and gave her daughter 7 million, she
оставила семь и дочке дала 7 млн она
bought something else there, she said something like an apartment there
что-то ещё купила там квартиру какую-то
Well  your eyes lit up 14 million
Ну у тебя ж глаза загорелись 14 млн
14 No, you just know, I know that when you are
14 Нет просто знаете я знаю что при
wounded they give 3 million, and
ранение дают 3 млн А
when you die they
при когда погибает
pay five. Well, how can there be less than two
платят пять та Ну как меньше чем два
wounds? 14 For me personally,
ранения не может быть тако 14 мне лично
my husband told me, my husband didn’t
вот мне мой муж говорил мой же муж не А
Why?  your husband told you he pays
зачем тебе муж говорил выплачивает
when I don’t remember, we get paid for the payments, we
при я не помню мы получается за выплаты
just started talking, he says, well, he
просто заговорили он говорит ну
pays so much every month A And I
ежемесячно платит там столько-то А И всё
list everything else, I say Why are you upset with
остальное перечисляю я говорю Зачем ты
me about this, he’s upset, he
мне вот это вот ня расстраиваешься он
Tai Well,
Тай Ну
what do you have, you have an apartment with a
что у вас у вас квартира в
mortgage  we are rented rented Yes, I understand.
ипотеке у нас съёмная съёмная Да понял А
How much does an apartment cost, for example, the kind you want to
сколько стоит квартира например такая
buy for yourself? Well, I looked at an ad in the
купить Ну вот я смотрела объявление в
building opposite, a three-room apartment
доме на против трёхкомнатная квартира
with good repairs is sold for
достаточно с хорошим ремон продаётся за
2 million for 2 million. That is, in principle, if your
2 млн за 2 млн То есть в принципе если
husband gets injured, you can buy a
муж получает ранение Вы можете купить
three-room
трёхкомнатную
apartment Well  exactly in Krasny Sulin Yes, in
квартиру Ну именно в Красном Сулине Да в
Rostov, of course, only here Well, yes, you
Ростове конечно здесь только Ну да у вас
can do it Well, it’s a small
получается Ну это там это небольшой
town there, it’s 20,000 dollars, it’s
городок это 20.000 долларов получается
our American money, yes, the money is 2 million, that
наши американские да деньги 2 млн да то
is, for 20,000 dollars you can
есть за 20.000 долларов Вы можете там
buy a three-room apartment there Well, yes,
купить трёхкомнатную квартиру Ну да
because that is, it turns out  If a
потому что то есть получается Если живёт
family lives in Rostov, then of course you can’t buy it there
в Ростове семья то конечно там не купишь
for an injury, and there will still be a million
за ранение а там ещё и миллион
left. Well, well, we do
останется Ну вот Ну мы всё равно Вот
n’t care. As long as he’s there, like the money we’ll receive, he’ll buy it for himself, I don’t remember, he was going to buy it, I
я не помню он собирался покупать о
called it  I listened to this,
называл я это прослушал
of course, and which money will then be
естествено и которые деньги потом будут
received by me, I’ll just put it aside,
получать я просто буду откладывать уже
let us have But the money is put aside
пусть у нас Бут отложены деньги на
just in case
всякий случай
there And if, for example, well, maybe life will be So an
там А если например ну может быт Так что
arrival will tear off his leg, like, well, you
будет прилёт ему оторвёт ногу типа ну вы
’ll let him use this money for treatment
же эти деньги на лечение будете ему
and not  I already have dates for the apartment
пускать а не на квартиру уже
Well, somehow some kind of business plan is a little bit
Ну как-то какой-то бизнес-план немножко
In short, it’s not
Короче не это
unreliable Well, there are some wives,
ненадёжный Ну есть которые жёны
I saw an example like this, I don’t remember
вот я видела пример такой я не помню
Where it came from that her husband’s arm
Откуда это было то что у мужа Там руку
was torn off and she received payments for
оторвала и ей пришли выплаты за
it
это ина
in  treatment, my husband
на лечение муж вообще
didn’t
ничего не
send anything at all and
отправила и
just disappeared with this money somewhere
просто скрылась с этими деньгами где-то
over the horizon and that’s all for you, your
за горизонтом и всё у тебя тыж у тебя аж
mood was lifted by this
настроение поднялось от этой
story. No, I’m just sitting there thinking,
истории Нет я просто сижу такая думаю ну
damn it’s your husband, like I understand
блин это твой муж типа я понимаю да то
that he’s missing an arm  now Well, what can you do,
что он без руки теперь Ну что поделаешь
it’s your husband
это же твой муж
and there are many many such stories. Yes, the
а много много таких историй Да что
wife really left with the money.
действительно жена с деньгами
I no, this is the only time I see this
свалила Я нет я единственный раз вижу э
story. Well, of course I
историю Ну это конечно я
know, I know that in the Rostov region I
знаю я знаю что в Ростовской области я
don’t remember only where the girl had a
не помню только где у девочки там
house left there  the father and the father of the father
дома от отца а отец наис отца нас
sent us away; the father died and the girl seemed to be with a
отправили отец погиб и девочка как бы с
guardian or with her mother. I don’t
опекуном или с матерью Я уже не
remember, I wanted to enter into an inheritance and
помню хотела вступить в наследство и
take this half, and there was some
забрать эту половину а там какой-то
guy like that. But no, it’s all like, I’ll
дяденька Такой типа А нет всё типа я те
tell you. Well, everything was decided through the court  and they gave
скажу Ну через суд всё решили и вернули
this girl back half of it. Well, yes, because
этой девочке половину Ну да потому что
it was her father who died, really, and not her uncle,
это ж её батя умер правда а не дядя
as
как
if I knew other stories in Russia
бы я я знаю ещё такие истории в России
like that
типа было что
the mother of this deceased and the wife of the deceased fought.
мама этого погибшего и жена погибшего
In short, who
бились Короче кому выплаты
will get the payments in general, in fact, the wife, in fact, the
достанутся вообще по факту жене по факту
wife,
жене
yes  yes, we pay his wife Or maybe his mother, well,
да да выплачиваем жене А может маме ну
you found out because maybe if he
ты узнавала потому что может если он
dies, he paid his mother. You have a
погибнет маме его выплатил У тебя
good relationship with his mother, why did you
хорошие отношения с мамой
hesitate?
его да что так замялась
Yes, I confused him with my mother and that’s it. Well, it
Да я с такая перепутала со своей мамой и
turns out well. What if, like,
всё Ну хорошо получается А если Типа
what happens to his mother?  payments are made
если выйдет что его маме выплаты делают
and not to you. How will you then resolve
и не тебе Как ты будешь тогда решать
this issue? Yes, let her have it. Well, she’s his
этот вопрос Да пусть ей будет Ну она его
mother, what can I do about it? And you
мать что я могу сделать с этим А у вас
have children, no, I understand. Well, yes, because if there were
есть нет Поня Ну да потому если были
children for the children, a
дети же для дете
million damn it’s just you, in principle,
млн блин просто ты ты в принципе
in principle, if I received
е в принципе если бы мне пришли бы
payments there from Independence,
выплаты там Независимости
God forbid, no matter how much there is, of course, if he
сколько там не дай Бог Конечно если он
died, then I would share this money
погиб бы то я бы поделила бы эти деньги
with his mother because, well, this is his
с его мамы потому что ну это его
mother. Why,
мать А зачем
well, let me be smart too.
а ну пусть Уменя тоже будет я Подожди
Wait, he’s a grown man.  how old is he?
нуре Он взрослый мужик ему сколько
23 23 how old are
лет 23 23 тебе
you?
сколько 21 Ну тебе 21 Ты молодая лучше
Well, I understand, well, this is
ти Да ну это ти Ну я понимаю ну это же
his mother, she also raised him, she’s
его мать она же его тоже воспитывала она
also worried about him, she’s also
же тоже за него вот переживает она тоже
worried about him,
за него вот волнуется
like there’s also an aunt there. Maybe, maybe
типа там ещё и тётя Может есть то может
the aunt will also say, I was
тётя тоже скажет я
worried. Well, an aunt is an aunt, and a mother
волновалась Ну тётя - это тётя А мать -
is  his mother gave birth to him Well, yes, does he have a grandmother
это мать мать его рожала Ну да а бабушка
or has Nuri’s grandmother given birth to his mother,
него или уже Нури бабушка рожала маму
it’s also a chain the grandmother will tell me the
это же тоже цепочка бабушка скажет мне
same thing, like I
тоже типа
need it No, well, under the conditions But it will somehow
нужно Не ну прих условиях Но это как-то
be ugly
будет некрасиво то
what I took and spent all the money for, that
что я взяла и за хпала все деньги да то
is  I need half for my mother, well, in all conscience,
есть надо половину маме ну по совести
it’s half to give to my mother.
это половину маме отдать
Yes, I’d rather act in good conscience, divide
Да я лучше по совести поступлю поделю
this money in half, and look, we
эти деньги пополам и А смотри вот
can buy it. Where would you spend
наме можно купить куда бы ты потратила
that kind of money because it’s a lot of
такие деньги потому что это большие
money?
деньги
Well, first of all, I would buy myself
Да ну во-первых бы я себе купила
an apartment because  Well, it’s
квартиру потому что ну как
like over time you need to settle somewhere in one
бы со временем нужно где-то на одном
place, not live in a rented apartment all the time,
месте остановиться не жить всё время на
but for the rest it’s a lot of
квартире а на остальное это ж куча
money. But this money is just lying around, it’s just going to
денег Бут эти деньги Ну если они лежат
burn up, tomorrow there will be some kind of
просто они сгорят завтра будет какая-то
inflation and everyone needs something at once -  then a
инфляция и всё надо сразу их что-то
car in everyday life You have a
автомобиль быт У тебя есть
license No, well, I would pass the license and buy a
права Нет ну сдала бы на права купила бы
car Well, yes, for
автомобиль Ну это
now I can think about it But by the way, well,
да пока я об этом думать могу А кстати
for example, what kind of car would you
вот Ну например ты бы какую машину
buy if this
купила вот если бы позволяли вот эти
payment money allowed? I would buy myself a Toyota Camry
выплаты Я бы себе купила Toyota Camry
Toyota  Camry is not bad, yes And how much does your
Toyota Camry нехила да А сколько у вас
Toyota Camry cost now?
Toyota Camry сейчас стоит
Oh, by the way, I don’t know, but in general I’m
О кстати я не знаю ну вообще у меня
attracted to BMW. That’s how
привлекает вот BMW Вот который
old they are, they’re actually so cool
старенькие такие они пря вообще такие
and they’re inexpensive even now.
классные и они недорогие ещё сейчас поло
Damn, well, it turns out Toyota hry. I don’t know.
Блин ну получается Toyota hry Я не знаю
Or is it enough?  how much does it
Или она хватит ну сколько она
cost a lot a lot yes Just if it’s toota
стоит много много да Просто если toota
hry then maybe there won’t be enough for an apartment in Rostov
hry то тогда может на квартиру в Ростове
I don’t want to move to Rostov But that’s all
Я в Ростов не хочу переезжать А ну всё
if you if you buy for twenty
если ты если ты За двадцатку покупаешь
This is across the road uh for 20,000
Вот это через дорогу ээ за 20.000
dollars like for 2 million rubles you buy that
долларов типа за 2 млн руб покупаешь ту
three-room used apartment Yes, and then Toyota,
трёхкомнатную бэушную Да и тогда Toyota
I can even buy this apartment And
я даже могу эту квартиру выкупить А это
how much does it cost Oh, I
сколько стоит Ой я с хозяйкой насчёт
didn’t ask the owner about this
этого не интересовала
how much, well, you have one two three
сколько ну это у тебя одно двух трёх
room three three Well, you buy that
комнатное трёх трёх Ну всё покупаешь ту
three-ruble ruble, it will also be in the region of twenty
трёшку она тоже будет в районе двадцатки
Well, 2 million
Да ну 2 млн
True Well, about yes, yes,
Правда Ну примерно да то да прям про
there is no such thing about such expensive housing, well, that is,
такого дорогого жилья нету ну то есть
look, it turns out If 14 million is
смотри да получается Если 14 млн - это
seven, the mother takes it, the mother
семь мама забирает уже мама она Сама
decides for herself what she will spend it on. Yes, 2 million
решает на что она потратит Да 2 млн
goes to the apartment and five is left for
уходит на квартиру и пять остаётся за
five Well, I don’t know  5 million is 50,000
пять Ну я не знаю 5 млн - это 50.000
dollars or you can
долларов или ёту Camry
buy this Camry Well, in general, I would like to have a BMW,
купишь Ну вообще я хотела бы себе BMW
put one like this and this is how much it costs
стави такой вот это вот а сколько стоит
and this is a camera this is
а это камера это
up to a million I seem to know Well, that’s it
коне до миллиона Я вроде бы знаешь А ну
That is, you’re like a used one Yes, you want
всё То есть ты типа бэушную Да хочешь
a Mvsh Well, I understand  then it turns out Well, two
мвш Ну да понял то получается Ну два Ну
Well, anyway, look, if it was 14 million, 7
так всё равно смотри если было 14 млн 7
million, your mother is seven, you buy
млн маме семь тебе Ты за две покупаешь
an apartment for two, for a million cars, you still have 4
квартиру за миллион машин ещё остаётся 4
million left. Well, I would open all the business for now,
млн у тебя Ну ты я пока всё бизнес бы
and what kind of
откры а какой
business is this some kind of confectionery?
бизнес это кондитерскую какую-нибудь А
Well,  yes, you’re a condiment cook, like And what would
ну да ты ж повар конди пор типа А как бы
you call yours, this
ты назвала свою вот эту
pastry chef, these are
кондитер вот эти
also And like, you open your pick-up point
ещё А типа открываешь свой пункт выдачи
Yes
Да
Dan, your sound disappears when
Дан у тебя у тебя пропадает звук когда
you
ты
move Well, now say
двигаешься А ну сейчас говори
it, maybe it just turns out that way, well, the
е а может бы так просто получается ну
pick-up point  You're not very good at NM, you don't
пункт выдачи Ты не сильно на НМ это на
cook it, but here's the confectionery shop. What would you
варишь А вот кондитерская А как бы ты
call it? You thought you were thinking about what you'd
назвал ты думала ты думала как ты
call your confectionery
назовёшь свою кондитерскую
shop. By the way, I haven't thought about it yet.
кстати об этом ещ не заду
Well, I don't know, honestly,
Ну не знаю честно
that's where it
вот
all
во всё
begins. Well, you know something,
начинается Ну что-то вот знаете со
sweets are
сладким
connected with sweets, sweet boy  can you call it that
связаны сладкий мальчик можно так
anyway? I
назвать вобще Я назвала
forgot to name it, but think about it, I’m
это забыла да подумай мне
interested, well, the sweet world is what
интересно ну сладкий мир это вообще
ZAZ is like. Well, you know,
ЗАЗ Ну знаете
like, there’s like a cafe in Rostov,
типа вот по типу есть э кафе в Ростове
cupcake Yeah, that’s about something connected with this, that’s
кекс Угу Вот примерно вот что-то с этим
what I’m
связанно вот такое вот то что сейчас я
thinking of now  I can’t It’s cool, you
придумать что не могу Прикольно можно
know, look, well, how much do
знаешь вот смотри м ну сколько у вас
cakes cost about these things? How much do
пироженое вот эти всякие штучки Сколько
confectionery cost? I’m
стоят кондитерские изделия
stuck for the second time. So we’ll catch her for the third time,
зависла Так мы поймаем её третий раз вот
this is like, peeps, comment, let’s continue. It’s
это лайк пидпис комент продолжаем Это
just because my husband is just
просто смотрите от того что муж просто
a shift worker, like I am her.  promoted Yes, and how did she
вахтовик как я её раскрутил Да и как она
when I just saw when I said that
когда я просто увидел когда я сказал что
14 million is being given out for a dead husband, his
14 млн выдают за мужа мёртвого у него аж
eyes already lit up, put a plus if you
глаза загорелись поставьте плюс если Вы
saw it, yes, 14 million that I heard Again, yes,
это видели да 14 млн та я слышал Опять
and she already overloaded the counter in
да и у неё аж счётчик перегрузил в
her head, damn it, and she’s like that  calmly divides
голове блин и она так спокойно делит
the money for a potentially murdered husband Well,
деньги за убитого потенциально мужа Ну
okay, to my mother, what about garlic, so I
ладно сем маме что по чесноку так две
’m buying two houses, in short, a lemon for bmsh Yes, there’s still
хаты покупаю короче лимон на бмш Да ещё
4 ml left for the business, I’ll open a confectionery shop,
4 мл остатся бизнес открою кондитерскую
just a master of promotion, you know Archie,
просто мастер раскрутки вы знаете Арчи
who I just don’t talk about
который я просто тут не общаюсь о
politics here Yes, promote, pull out the whole shower.
политике Да раскрутить вытянуть всю душ
for this like subscribe comment and
Вот за это лайк подписка коммент и
send this video to your friends it’s just that
скиньте это видео друзьям просто вот
you owe it to
обязаны чтобы вы же хотите чтобы
you to make this lady’s wish come true so that she
исполнила себе желание чтобы она
gets an apartment
получила квартиру
bhu and opens a pastry shop with the name
бху и кондитерскую открыла с названием
g letter to my Telegram directly at once axis
г пись на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось
VN
ВН
apok tse duzhe and  It’s very respectful that YouTube took
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ODS in your ban and I
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too many videos to people often I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali have an operational link to
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
write right away and Popik is there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram okrim video also the same cikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж е цикава и
korisna information and  we will
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
letter
пись а